Thank you Chaz! And we’d like to give a...
Good evening!
Mark: Buenas noches!
Bonsoir!
And in Fjarl, Ah hrueg!
That’s right! And my moustache... is still a moustache!
I agree, Mark!
Wanda: How are you not fired yet?
Mark: It’s a mystery!
Okay, and back to our topic, that doesn’t involve
Mark’s Gross Facial Hair!
We are here to interview students of Sunnypeg High, about this gaggle of trouble!
Yes, this duckdaster definitely gives me goosebumps!
Let’s take a gander, shall we?
Here’s someone now! Excuse me, do you have a moment?
Yes, I guess I’ve got time. What is it?
Okay, how do you feel about the mayor’s plans to turn into a Canadian Goose and provoke rampage?
Um, honestly, I don’t care, as long as, like, he shuts down the school or something.
But don’t you know his plans to eat us all?
Umm... I don’t even think I’m going to make it to grade ten, so...
Okay, that’s not good...
Yep...
Oh my god! Is that a camera?! Hi!!
Ah hem!
Uh, excuse me! Kind of busy here!
Goose!
What is your childhood trauma? Ugh!
What he means is that I’m Wanda and this is Mark of #WpgDrBuffy News.
We’re here to interview students. Your name?
Oh, it’s just Claudelia! What did you want to ask me?
Scott Gillingham, the mayor of Winnipeg, apparently has plans...
.... to change into a giant Canadian Goose and take over the town.
How do you feel about this now, Claudelia?
Well, it doesn’t concern me, so like, not my problem!
As long as he doesn’t step on my Porsche.
But don’t you know about his plans to gobble us all up like bugs in Assiniboine Park?
Doesn’t matter to me! My father will pay him.
I wish I had a Porsche...
Well too bad! I do, and you don’t!
Wait, do you at least like my moustache?
Uh, no. It looks like a sewer drain slowly gargling out garbage.