Craving a flavour explosion?
Come on down to Doublemeat Palace...
... where taste meets tradition!
At Doublemeat Palace, we’re serving up the legendary Doublemeat Medley!
Two juicy patties, one unforgettable bite!
Oh, what cards do you think we’re gonna get?
I got The Gentlemen!
Wow!
What’s our secret ingredient?
Well, it’s a secret!
But trust us, it’s not what you think!
I just can’t get enough of the Cherry Palace Pot Pie!
It’s not cherry, Vera! It’ s apple!
It says right on the box, you blind old bat!
I think it’s made out of vegetables!
I can taste it, I can!
You’re full of beans!
I think it’s full of beans!
You two argue about this every time!
Can’t we just enjoy the food?
No!
Oh, you goat!
Why are you two bickering like this?
Cut! Cut!
We’re losing daylight here!
I’ll punch the daylights out of you!
Doublemeat Palace
Where every bite is a mystery, and every meal is an adventure!
This is the fiftieth take!
I have pie in my hair.
Serves you right!